

#### **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

Human Resources professional with experience in small and medium sized companies. Extensive HR Business Partnership background, including experience in management coaching, talent management, performance management, career development, conflict resolution, compensation, and HR program development. Skilled in building credible relationships with business leaders and assisting them in developing HR initiatives that align with business goals and deliverables.

## **EXPERIENCE**

**Medical Leave of Absence** 

April 2018 - Present

Sr. Manager, HR Business Partnership

Redfin/ Seattle, WA /November 2017 - April 2018

Sr. HR Business Partner

Redfin/Seattle, WA / February 2016 – November 2017

Lead HR for Redfin's Business Operations teams, including Engineering, Product, Communications and Corporate Functions (~400 domestically, 2 locations)

- Developed and drove people strategy for client groups in alignment with company goals.
- Partnered with business leaders to build out and streamline HR
  infrastructure across the Business Operations teams, including
  compensation design, performance review processes, employee
  engagement surveys, internal titling and leveling and talent review
  practices.
- Managed people strategy for the Business Operations teams during and post IPO.

Sr. Lead HR Business Partner

Sr. HR Business Partner

**HR Business Partner** 

**HR** Coordinator

Electronic Arts / Redwood Shores, CA / May 2011 – February 2016

Supported EA's Digital Platform Engineering teams, including the Big Data, Mobile Platform, Commerce, Identity, and System Engineering Test teams (~500 globally) Previously HR Business Partner to The Maxis Game Team organization (~300 employees globally)

- Developed and drove the people strategy for client groups; analyzed and presented information to the management team that enabled sound decisions as well as drove and supported HR initiatives.
- Drove systemic organizational and people strategies that were aligned to the business strategy, including: employee relations, manager coaching, compensation, legal compliance, talent and performance management, training and career development.

#### **CONTACTS**

Email: kbost111@gmail.com

**Phone:** 925-918-0658

Address: 21743 Orange Avenue

Castro Valley, CA 94546

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/kellybostwick

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

HR Policy, Process & Systems

Design

Performance Management

Transformation

Engagement Survey Design, Communication, and Action Planning Strategy

# **SKILLS**

Manager Coaching

**Talent Management** 

**Succession Planning** 

Change Management

**Employee Relations** 

**HR** Analytics

Microsoft Office Suite

## **EDUCATION**

## **Masters Business Administration**

St. Mary's College, Moraga, CA September 2013

## **Bachelor of Arts / Psychology**

University of California, Berkeley Berkeley, CA, August 2006

#### **HR** Generalist

Zachary's Chicago Pizza Inc. / Berkeley, CA / July 2009 – May 2011

Sole HR Generalist to small retail restaurant chain (~150 domestically, 3 locations)

- Worked closely on organizational decisions and strategies with CEO,
   General Management, and Board of Directors and provided recommendations.
- Managed the Employee Stock Ownership Plan and transitioned the business to 100% employee ownership.
- Developed and implemented all HR processes and roadmaps.
- Handled all recruiting and retention matters.
- Managed benefit programs and offerings, including qualified 401(k) and Employee Stock Ownership Plans.
- Handled all employee inquires.
- Managed HRIS, payroll, and compensation plans using ADP suite of products.

#### **HR** Generalist

Pella Window and Door / Livermore, CA / May 2007 – July 2009

HR Support to corporate offices and 10 showroom locations across California, Nevada and Oregon (~250 domestically)

- Successfully supported performance and compensation initiatives,
   employee and manager training, workers compensation claims, recruiting,
   and benefits management, enrollment, and renewal
- Provided leadership, guidance, and support to management team
- Project managed short-term and annually recurring HR projects and initiatives
- Responsible for the research and development of company compensation plans
- Responsible for New Hire Orientation development and administration
- Managed matters of progressive discipline
- Managed HRIS, payroll, and Sales Team commission plans using ADP suite of products

## **TECHNICAL**

Workday
Microsoft Suite
ADP HRIS Systems
ADP Payroll Systems
Confluence

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

#### **PHR**

September 2012